http://www.erion.co.uk/AboutUs/privacypolicy.html

Samba Training Implementing Samba
Implementing Samba (3 day)
Background
Erion Limited ( Erion ,
we ,
our
or
us) understand that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your personal data is used. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who provides us with personal information when they:
visit our websites ( our Sites )
use our educational or consultancy services (together the
Services)
communicate with us.
We only collect and use your personal data as described in this Privacy Policy. Any personal data we collect will only be used as permitted by law.
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it.
1 Information About Us
Our Sites and Services are owned and operated by Erion Limited, a limited company, registered in England under company number 3521142.
Registered address: Erion Ltd, Newtons, 49 Coniscliffe Road, Darlington, County Durham, DL3 7EH, UK.
Main trading address: Erion Ltd, An Cala, Inverkirkaig, Lochinver, Sutherland, IV27 4LR, UK
VAT number: GB 698 3633 78.
Data Controller: Erion Limited.
Data Controller Contact Email address: privacyanddata@erion.co.uk.
Telephone number: +44 (0)1422 207000.
Postal address: Erion Ltd, An Cala, Inverkirkaig, Lochinver, Sutherland, IV27 4LR, UK.
We are regulated by the Information Commissioner s Office (ICO).
Our ICO registration reference is ZA335805.
2 What Does This Policy Cover?
This Privacy Policy applies to your use of our Sites and Services. Our Sites may contain links to other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
3 What Is Personal Data?
Personal data is defined by the General Data Protection Regulation (EU Regulation 2016/679) (the
GDPR ) and the Data Protection Act 2018 (collectively,
the Data Protection Legislation ) as
any information relating to an identifiable person who can be directly or indirectly identified in particular by reference to an identifier .
Personal data is, in simpler terms, any information about you that enables you to be identified. Personal data covers obvious information such as your name and contact details, but it also covers less obvious information such as identification numbers, electronic location data, and other online identifiers.
4 What Are My Rights?
Under the Data Protection Legislation, you have the following rights, which we will always work to uphold:
The right to be informed about our collection and use of your personal data. This Privacy Policy should tell you everything you need to know, but you can always contact us to find out more or to ask any questions using the details in Part 10.
The right to access the personal data we hold about you. Part 9 will tell you how to do this.
The right to have your personal data rectified if any of your personal data held by us is inaccurate or incomplete. Please contact us using the details in Part 10 to find out more.
The right to be forgotten, i.e. the right to ask us to delete or otherwise dispose of any of your personal data that we hold. Please contact us using the details in Part 10 to find out more.
The right to restrict (i.e. prevent) the processing of your personal data.
The right to object to us using your personal data for a particular purpose or purposes.
The right to withdraw consent. This means that, if we are relying on your consent as the legal basis for using your personal data, you are free to withdraw that consent at any time.
The right to data portability. This means that, if you have provided personal data to us directly, we are using it with your consent or for the performance of a contract, and that data is processed using automated means, you can ask us for a copy of that personal data to re-use with another service or business in many cases.
Rights relating to automated decision-making and profiling. we do not use your personal data in this way.
For more information about our use of your personal data or exercising your rights as outlined above, please contact us using the details provided in Part 10.
It is important that your personal data is kept accurate and up to date. If any of the personal data we hold about you changes, please keep us informed as long as we have that data.
Further information about your rights can also be obtained from the Information Commissioner s Office or your local Citizens Advice Bureau.
If you have any cause for complaint about our use of your personal data, you have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner s Office. we would welcome the opportunity to resolve your concerns ourselves, however, so please contact us first, using the details in Part 10.
5 What Personal Data Do You Collect and How?
Subject to the following, we do not collect any personal data from you. We do not place cookies on your computer or device, nor do we use any other means of data collection.
Our Sites collect certain information automatically, including your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and certain other non-personal data about your computer or device such as your operating system type or version, and display resolution.
If you send us a letter, an email or complete one of the forms on one of our Sites, we may collect your name, your email address, and any other information which you choose to give us. For the purposes of the Data Protection Legislation, we are the data controller responsible for such personal data.
Some of the personal information that you choose to give us may include sensitive personal information, such as health-related information to ensure that we can provide the necessary duty of care during the provision of our Services to you.
The lawful basis under the Data Protection Legislation that allows us to use such information is article 6(1)(f) of the GDPR which allows us to process personal data when it is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests, in this case, the proper operation and functionality of our Sites and the provision of our Services. If you contact us as described above, you will be required to consent to our use of your personal data to contact you. In this case, our lawful basis for using your personal data will be article 6(1)(a) of the GDPR, which allows us to use your personal data with your consent for a particular purpose or purposes.
6 How Do You Use My Personal Data?
Where we collect any personal data, it will be processed and stored securely, for no longer than is necessary in light of the reason(s) for which it was first collected. we will comply with our obligations and safeguard your rights under the Data Protection Legislation at all times. For more details on security see Part 7, below.
As stated above, we do not generally collect any personal data directly from you, but if you contact us and we obtain your personal details from your letter, email or a contact form on one of our Sites, we may use them to respond to you. We may also use this information in the process of providing our Services to you. The other technical data referred to above is necessary for the technical operation of our Sites and will not normally be used in any way to personally identify you.
We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested or to comply with applicable legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements).
We will not share any of your personal data with any third parties for any purposes other than where it is required to
deliver Services or provide information that you have requested from us (for example, to training venues that require names of delegates and other personal information such as dietary requirements)
partners that we work with to provide our Services
meet our obligations to your employer (for example, if they are paying for training that you attend, and they request course attendance statistics and copies of your evaluations)
meet our legal and regulatory obligations
any other person or organisation that you consent to use sharing your data with
With your permission and/or where permitted by law, we may also use your personal data for marketing purposes, which may include contacting you by email or telephone with information, news, and offers on our Services. You will not be sent any unlawful marketing or spam. We will always work to fully protect your rights and comply with our obligations under the Data Protection Legislation and the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, and you will always have the opportunity to opt-out. We will always obtain your express opt-in consent before sharing your personal data with third parties for marketing purposes and you will be able to opt-out at any time.
7 How and Where Do You Store My Data?
We will store most of your personal data in the UK. This means that it will be fully protected under the Data Protection Legislation.
For some of our Services, we may store some or all of your personal data in, countries outside of the EEA. However, we have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your personal information will remain protected in accordance with this Privacy Notice. These measures include transferring your personal data to third parties who are located in a country which the European Commission has determined has data protection laws that are at least as protective as those in Europe, and transferring your personal data to third parties who have entered into standard contractual clauses with us. For more information about these safeguards please contact us using the contact details provided below.
Personal data security is essential to us, and to protect personal data, we take the following measures:
limiting access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors, and other third parties with a legitimate need to know and ensuring that they are subject to duties of confidentiality;
procedures for dealing with data breaches (the accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorised disclosure of, or access to, your personal data) including notifying you and/or the Information Commissioner s Office where we are legally required to do so.
8 Do You Share My Personal Data?
We will not share any of your personal data with any third parties for any purposes, subject to the following exceptions.
We may share your personal data with:
training venue providers when you attend one of our training courses;
virtual classroom providers when you attend one of our virtual training courses;
your employer where they have instructed as or funded the Services provided by us.
The purchasing organisation when they request evaluations, feedback, comments or attendance statistics.
Any person or organisation that you consent with us to the disclosure.
If any of your personal data is transferred to a third party, as described above, we will take steps to ensure that your personal data is handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, our obligations, and the third party s obligations under the law, as described above in Part 7.
If any personal data is transferred outside of the EEA, we will take suitable steps in order to ensure that your personal data is treated just as safely and securely as it would be within the UK and under the Data Protection Legislation, as explained above in Part 7.
If we sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or assets, your personal data may be transferred to a third party. Any new owner of our business may continue to use your personal data in the same way(s) that we have used it, as specified in this Privacy Policy (i.e. to communicate with you).
In some limited circumstances, we may be legally required to share certain personal data, which might include yours, if we are involved in legal proceedings or complying with legal obligations, a court order, or the instructions of a government authority.
9 How Can I Access My Personal Data?
If you want to know what personal data we have about you, you can ask us for details of that personal data and for a copy of it (where any such personal data is held). This is known as a
subject access request .
All subject access requests should be made in writing and sent to the email or postal addresses shown in Part 10.
There is not normally any charge for a subject access request. If your request is
manifestly unfounded or excessive
(for example, if you make repetitive requests) a fee may be charged to cover our administrative costs in responding.
We will respond to your subject access request in accordance with the applicable data protection laws. You will be kept fully informed of our progress.
10 How Do I Contact You?
To contact us about anything to do with your personal data and data protection, including to make a subject access request, please use the following details for the attention of the Data Protection Officer:
Email address: privacyanddata@erion.co.uk.
Telephone number: +44 (0)1422 207000.
Postal Address: Erion Ltd, An Cala, Inverkirkaig, Lochinver, Sutherland, IV27 4LR, UK.
11 Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. This may be necessary, for example, if the law changes, or if we change our business in a way that affects personal data protection.
Any changes will be immediately posted on our Sites and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of our Sites following the alterations. we recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up to date. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 3rd October 2019.
About Us
Erion Clients
Other Erion Services
Erion IPv6 Blog
Contact Us
